I was in the industry before.
I decided to just get relicensed up give it another whirl, even though everybody was
telling me it's a horrible time was lucky to get deployed to Beryl most recently the
Helene deal.
I'd prepared with everything through this class.
I went down to even buying the same camera that you recommended.
And just, mean, it was just to the T
was a great deployment.
kept me on, you know, quite a long time.
know, at the end there wasn't many of us left, so.
my files on Beryl were not that great.
You know, I realize that now.
Photos were probably lacking big time.
after taking Fast Track, everything really improved.
what your program did for me was really made me a lot more efficient and my files a lot
more enjoyable for other people that were reviewing them.
know now after taking these other people's files and having to get them closed and
reconciled estimates and.
I know why you won't get invited back to a storm if you're if all that stuff's not it's
not good, you know
And my whole goal going into this deployment, was noticed and to get somebody's attention,
kept asking my trainer, where do I stand?
who else is closing some claims, you know, and and they, and they just said, you need to
stop worrying about it.
You're in no danger.
for a new adjuster
They may not know the why at the time, if they really study your program and take that
stuff to heart and use it and literally follow it, just do it without knowing why you're
doing it and you'll know later on.