it was fast.
didn't mean to go through it as quick as I did, but I finished one and I'm I want see what
this next one is.
it was really good it did what I want, what I needed it to do.
I felt like there's a lot of pieces of the puzzle and I didn't know how, how they fit
together.
I got to see the box on the front of the puzzle cover
I always want to be as prepared as I possibly can be for what's coming.
And that makes me feel a whole lot better.
I'd love to do this live but the recorded, I've gone back numerous times it's a lot of
information to take in.
And I realized that once I was kind of being tested on it, it was like, I need to go take
some of this back in again.
So I think that's a real valuable asset to have.
to schedule your first deployment.
Do this, do this, do this, it's just the steps.
all the little things that I see are going to help me build speed down the road, whether
it's scheduling, the macros, the templates, all that type of stuff that I could see could
really start cutting a lot of time so you can push a lot more claims out.
when I laid out that credit card, was like, that was a lot of money I just spent right
there, but I have no regrets whatsoever.
fast track stuff plus the Xactimate level one and two trainings, all that combined.
I feel I got a good bargain.
absolutely, yeah, yeah, no hesitation.